Do my eyes deceive me, or are you
wearing skates?
Uh you'll see what these can do.
Nice skates. Very cute. You going to
swap those out before we get to the
gunfight?
Uh you'll see what these can do.
Y'all, our teammate's wearing skates to
a gunfight.
Uh you'll see what these can do.
That rifle's
That rifle's a fine piece of work. Looks
a little unwieldy, though.
Perhaps, in the hands of an amateur.
That's a lot of armor.
Though, I guess you are a pretty big
target.
I GUESS I AM.
OH, with a grumpy dwarf in a Halloween
costume on our side, how can we lose?
Our chief cowardice.
Hm.
One shot,
one kill.
You know what happens to those who mock
me.
You know, I saved Jessie's life once.
Am I supposed to be thankful for that?
I know what it is to leave behind a past
you are not proud of.
So, let's focus on the future, hm?
Hey, man. Happy to have you.
I've had bad luck with teams, but this
one seems all right.
Yeah, that's the spirit.
How do you THINK YOUR FANCY JUMPSUIT
WOULD FARE AGAINST MY HAMMER?
ALL THE armor in the world can't save
you from a well-placed bullet.
Stay behind me. I will keep you safe.
Yeah, thanks, but I already have a
bodyguard.
Where did the medic like you learn to
handle a weapon like that?
The number of battlefields I've seen, I
was bound to pick something up.
I saw you at Luna's Cabaret the other
evening.
Would you care to go together sometime?
I prefer to attend events alone.
Apologies. I wouldn't wish to intrude.
Baptiste, was it?
How did a mercenary like yourself come
by such advanced technologies?
Oh, I just make use of what I find lying
around.
I wish we could get that immortality
field to work on my turret.
But then our enemies would have no
chance.
Such intriguing sonic displacement
technology.
Thanks. My dad invented it. You two
would get along great.
You need to stop telling those
RIDICULOUS STORIES, REINHARDT. NO ONE
BELIEVES THEY'RE REAL.
RIDICULOUS STORIES? MY TALES OF
ADVENTURE AND GLORY ARE ALL TRUE.
EVEN THE ONE ABOUT THE mad doctor and
the witch?
Especially that one.
Brave of you to show your face after
what happened in Monte Cristi.
Well, it is a pretty good face.
Hello, Baptiste. Think you can hide from
Talon forever?
You can send your people to find me, but
I'll find them first.
Our foes make such a nuisance of
themselves.
Is that an emotion I detect, Lacroix?
You're making too much noise.
It's not noise, it's music.
Very well, you're making too much music.